Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 10: Pins and Ribbons, 1895-2000; 8 boxes
  - 40th reunion pin, 1972; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1932" and "40th" in black; with a tiger; "JIM DONNELL" handwritten in black.
  - 45th reunion pin, 1977; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1932" and "45th Reunion" in black; with a tiger; "JIM DONNELL" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1933; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Green and round with "Alumni Parade 1933" in black.
    Class of 1933.
  - 15th reunion pin, 1948; 1 box (Box E.6)
    "Fifteenth Reunion" and "1933" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "Bob Clifford" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1934; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Light yellow and round with "Alumni Parade 1934" in navy.
    Class of 1934.
  - 59th reunion pin, 1993; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "1934" in black; a drawing of a tiger in black and orange; a label "1993" attached; "MARY ATWATERKEER" handwritten.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Marine and round with "Alumni Parade 1935" in black.
    Class of 1935.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Brown and round with "Alumni Parade 1935" in white.
    Class of 1936.
  - Reunion pin, 1935; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1935" in green.
    Class of 1937.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1941; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Fifth Reunion," "'36" and seven 36's in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1937 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1937" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1938 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round, patterned on the baseball; with "Alumni," "1937" and "Parade" in black; orange and black ribbon.
    Class of 1938.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1958; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1938" and "Twentieth Reunion" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1963; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1938," "25th Reunion" and "June 12-16 1963" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "AL HEINSOHN" handwritten in black.
  - 35th reunion pin, 1973; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1938," "35th Reunion" and "June 7-10 1973" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "AL HEINSOHN" handwritten in green.
  - Reunion pin, 1939; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1939" in blue.
  - 22nd reunion pin, 1961; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and oval with "1939" and "Reunion June, 1961" in black; the Princeton seal and motto.
    Class of 1939.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1979; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1939 'XLISSIMO,'" "Original Combine," "A. P. G. A." and "'38 '40' '41 '42" in black; the "original combine" seal. Probably the 40th reunion pin of the class of 1939.
  - Class of 1939 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Tiger and liquor bottle with "Vat 39".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1940; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Light yellow and round with "Alumni Parade 1940" in brown.
    Class of 1940.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1941; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with blue rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1941" in red.
    Class of 1941.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1942; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with red rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1942" in blue.
    Class of 1942.
  - 10th reunion pin, 1952; 1 box (Box E.6)
    coral and black and round with "1942," "Jerry Horton" and "10th Reunion" counter-shaded.
  - Class of 1942 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and black with "Friar" and "'42" in black.
  - 40th reunion pin, 1983; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Yellow and white and round; with "1943" and "40th Reunion June 2-4 1983" in black; "Augusta Radcliffe" handwritten in black.
    Class of 1943.
  - 39th reunion pin, 1983; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "1944" in black; a caricature of a tiger and a modified version of the Princeton seal and motto in black; a label "1983" attached.
    Class of 1944.
  - Reunion pin, 1983; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and yellow and round; with "'39, '40, '41, '42, '44," "Old Original Combine," and "Reunion June 2-4 1983" in black.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1995; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with the Princeton seal and motto; "John Kauffman" handwritten in black; a label "1995" attached.
    Class of 1945.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1946; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with orange rim; with "Alumni P-Rade 1946" in brown.
    Class of 1946.
  - Class of 1946 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Princeton University, "'46" and "Bicentennial Class" in black; the Princeton seal and motto; "Walt Snow" handwritten.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1966; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "20th Reunion" and "1946" in black; "Walt Snow" handwritten in black.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "46's/50th" "The Legendary Bicentennial Class" in black; "REID BADGETT" hand written in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1947; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Red and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1947" in black.
    Class of 1947.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1948; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1948" in black.
    Class of 1948.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1949; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1949" in black.
    Class of 1949.
  - Class of 1949 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and orange and round with "1949 Playboy" in black; a drawing of a tiger smoking and drinking.
  - Class of 1949 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "The Automated Man" and "49" in orange; "Dan Lutzeier" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1950; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1950" in black.
    Class of 1950.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1951; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1951" in counter-shade.
    Class of 1951.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1976; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "The Revolutionary 25th" and "June 3-6, 1976" in black; "1951" in orange.
  - 45th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and rectangular "Princeton" and "1951" in orange; "45th Reunion" in black; a label "1996"; "Wiley Anderson" handwritten in black; a drawing of a tiger in an 18th-century costume.
  - Reunion pin, 1952; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1952" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1953; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1953" in counter-shade.
  - Reunion pin, 1954; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1954" in black; orange ribbon, "June 1954" and "Old Guard" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1955; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1955" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, 1956; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1956" in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1980; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "'55/25th" in black.
    Class of 1955.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1985; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and black and round with "'55/30th" in white; a label "1985"; "Don Altmaier" handwritten in black.
  - 40th reunion pin, 1995; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "'55/40th" in black; a label "Tom Graham, Jr".
  - 40th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "The Great Class 40th" and "Princeton 250th"in black; a label "1996"; a drawing of a tiger in black and orange.
    Class of 1956.
  - Reunion pin, 1957; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Black and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1957" in orange.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1977; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Paint the town with '57 in '77" in black; a drawing of a tiger painting.
    Class of 1957.
  - Reunion pin, 1958; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Red and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1958" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1959; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Light yellow with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1959" in black.
    Class of 1959.
  - Reunion pin, 1960; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1960" in black.
    Class of 1960.
  - Reunion pin, 1961; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1961" in black.
    Class of 1961.
  - 10th reunion pin, 1971; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "'61 in '71" in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1986; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with orange rim; "Princeton Class of 1961 25th Reunion" in black; a drawing of a tiger in orange and black; a label "Minor 1986"; "Ashley Magargee '62" handwritten.
  - 35th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "35th Reunion Celebrating 250 Great Years" in orange and black; a label "1996"; "Mary Conner" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1962; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1962" in black.
    Class of 1962.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1963; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White with orange border. "Alumni P-Rade 1963" in black.
    Class of 1963.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1964; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Alumni P-Rade 1964" in black.
    Class of 1964.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1970; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Orange and round with "Princeton University," "'65" and "Fifth Reunion" in black; a label "1989" handwritten.
    Class of 1965.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1991; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in a bow-tie; a label "Minor 1991"; Kathryn Barrows" handwritten in black.
    Class of 1966.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in a hat; "Overall 30th" and "On the Road to 250" in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1967; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Black and round with "67" in tan.
    Class of 1967.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1992; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Gray and round with "Class of 1967," "Clear the Track" and "25th Reunion" in black; a label "1992"; "Dan White" handwritten in black.
  - Medallion, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
  - 25th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger on bicycle; "Saving the Wild Life. 1971's 25th Princeton's 250th" in orange and black; "Caley Schmierer" handwritten in black; a label "1996".
    Class of 1971.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger on bicycle; a handwritten name illegible.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1977; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and rectangular with a tiger wearing a baseball cap; "'72's 5th" written in black.
    Class of 1972.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "'79" in black.
    Class of 1979.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "The Class of 1980" in white.
    Class of 1980.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "PUP80" in white.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "P. U. 'Eighty One!" in brown and black.
    Class of 1981.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with a tiger drawn in orange; "Princeton '81" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Yellow and round with "PU 82" in white and black.
    Class of 1982.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with black rim; "83" in yellow and black.
    Class of 1983.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with two beer mugs bearing "8" and "3" in black; "I Survived Another Party" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange (faded) and black; round with "1984" in white.
    Class of 1984.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "1984... Is here" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with a tiger and "1985" in black.
    Class of 1985.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "We Made It! P '86" in black.
    Class of 1986.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "86" in black and with 3 tigers looking out of the holes of the numerals.
  - 10th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with "X" and "Marks the Spot" in black, over laid on "86" in orange".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1987" in orange.
    Class of 1987.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "Welcome to the Great Class of 1988 to the Alumni Council" in black.
    Class of 1988.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1989; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1989 Princeton University" in orange.
    Class of 1989.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1995; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger on a director's chair with a bullhorn marked "5th"; "Lights!," "Camera!," "Action!" in orange and black; "Josh Empson" handwritten in black; a label "1995".
    Class of 1990.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1991-2000; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "The Class of 1990 Princeton University" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1991; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1991 Princeton University" in orange.
    Class of 1991.
  - 60th reunion pin, 1987; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and rectangular with "Class of 1927" in orange; with a photograph of A. Whitaker (1927); "Al Whitaker" handwritten in black.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger; "Class of 1991 5th Reunion" in black.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1993; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1993 Princeton University" in orange.
    Class of 1993.
  - Reunion pin, 1993; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger seated on "93"; with "Gwen Prothro" in black; a label "1993".
  - Reunion pin, circa 1994; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a drawing of the Princeton seal; "94" in orange.
    Class of 1994.
  - Reunion pin, circa 1995; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "The Class of 1995 Princeton University" in orange.
    Class of 1995.
  - Reunion pin, 1994; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a drawing of Cleveland Tower and a tiger; "Graduate Alumni" in black and "94" watermarked in orange; a label "1994"; "Paul" handwritten in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1996; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a drawing of a tiger in Da Vinci's study mode; "Graduate Alumni," "1996 Reunion" in orange; "Deborah Schildkraut" handwritten in black; a label "1996".
  - Reunion pin, 1997; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with a drawing of a tiger in Da Vinci's study mode; "Graduate Alumni," "1997 Reunion" in orange; "Sue Kim" handwritten in black; a label "1997".
  - Graduate Alumni Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Conference" in black.
  - Alumni Council Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and rectangular with a drawing of a boat; "Alumni Council" handwritten in black.
  - National Alumni Association Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and rectangular with "Princeton University National Alumni Ass'n" in black; "Jerry Horton '42" inlaid.
  - Battle Monument Dedication Ribbon, 1922 June 9; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Red, white and blue, and round; "Usher Dedication of the Princeton Battle Monument June 9, 1922" in golden.
  - McCosh Pin, circa 1988; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with President J. McCosh's photograph inset; "1868--D. James McCosh, President, Educator, Philosopher--1888" in black.
  - Dickinson and Patton Pin, 1896; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with Presidents J. Dickinson's and F. L. Patton's photographs, with "Dickinson and Patton" in countercolor; "1746-1896" in black.
  - Championship Dinner Pin, 1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with a drawing of a tiger; "P. 36-H. 0 P. 25-Y.12 Championship Dinner New York City January 8th 1926" in black.
  - Communiversity Staff Pin, 1985; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a drawing of the FitzRandolph Gate and Nassau Hall; "Communiversity April 27, 1985 Staff" in black.
  - Princeton Parent Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with black rim; "I'm a Proud Princeton Parent" in black.
  - Beat Dartmouth Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and rectangular; "Beat Dartmouth" in black.
  - Beat Harvard Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round; "Beat Harvard" in black.
  - Beat Yale Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round; "Beat Yale" in black.
  - Bullish on Princeton Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and oval; "I'm Bullish on Princeton" in black.
  - Games Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round; "'B. T. C.!'" and "Compete! Games" in black.
  - Campaign for Princeton Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Round with Princeton seal in orange and black; "A Campaign for Princeton" in white.
  - Food is Energy Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with a tiger having am ice cream cone; "Food I$ Energy Don't Wa$te It!" in black.
  - Bring Back the Old Princeton Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "Bring Back the Old Princeton" in black.
  - Princeton Wrestling Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with "Save Princeton Wrestling" in orange.
  - Take Back the Night Pin, 1992; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Navy and round with "take back the night" mark; "Princeton Unite! Take Back the Night April 25, 1992" in white.
  - Project 83 Pin, 1983; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with a tiger; Orange "V" overlaid with "Project 83" in black.
  - Project 88 Pin, 1988; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with "Project Eighty Eight." in black, orange and white.
  - Project 89 Pin, 1989; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with "Project 89" in orange and black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Black and round with an orange band across, "Princeton" in black; orange and black ribbon attached.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze name tag with Princeton seal and motto on top; an insert typed "Timothy N. Pfeiffer".
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with orange and black rims; with a tiger.
  - Un-Curl Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with "Un-Curl" in black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and black; round with "Princeton" countershaded.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with unrecognized figures in black.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with black rim; "P" in black; "Brown -* *- Princeton" in black on orange ribbon.
  - St. Louis Alumni Pin, 1921; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with an orange bow on top; "National Alumni Ass'n Princeton University St. Louis February 11-12, 1921" in black; "Gordon Rentschler '07" handwritten with pencil.
  - Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round with black ruffle around.
  - Class of 1889 Ribbon, 1895; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and rectangular; "'89 Sexennial June 10th, 1895" in black.
    Class of 1889.
  - Ribbon, 1896; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and rectangular, with white pennant of Princeton seal and motto and "1746" and "1896," attached.
  - Pin, 1993; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with a tiger wearing sunglasses; "Princeton University Staff Picnic June 10, 1993" in black; with a purple ribbon attached, "Judge" in silver.
  - Class of 1871 Pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze with a tiger head; a orange and black ribbon with stars in black; a metal piece "71" hanging from the mouth of the tiger.
    Class of 1871.
- Series 12: Sports, 1876-1989; 12 boxes
  The Sports Series includes figurines, equipment, and clothing.
  - Baseball, 1876; 1 box (Box C.4)
    76 vs. 74, 76-7 74-4.
  - Basketball Tickets, 1966; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Feb 12, 1966. vs. Yale. About 50-60 tickets.
  - Cloth print, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Baseball player.
  - Cloth print, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Football player
  - Discus, 1896; 1 box (Box 27)
    AR.1996.086
    Robert Garrett 1897, threw this discus 95'7.5" and won first place at the first Olympic Games in modern times at Athens, Greece 1896. Note.0 It is unknown whether this discus or the unmounted one was the actual discus thrown. See Box C.02.
  - Discus, 1896; 1 box (Box C.2)
    Mounted Garrett discus used to win at the first Olympics of modern times at Athens, Greece. Note- it is unknown whether this discus or the mounted one was the actual discus thrown.
  - Figurine, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    Football player figurine. Black jersey with orange #6.
  - Figurine, Undated; 1 box (Box 40)
    Football player holding ball and wearing a Princeton pin.
  - Football, 1951; 1 box (Box 19)
    AR.2005.049
    Princeton 12 - Brown 0. Signed by members of the 1951 team including Dick Kazmaier '52
  - Football jersey, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
    Princeton football jersey. #70. Black with orange stripes and white numbers.
  - Football music player, Undated; 1 box (Box C.4)
    "Goin' Back"
  - Football Patch, 1989; 1 box (Box C.1)
    AR.1992.030
    "Princeton Tigers 1000 Nov 6, 1869 - Oct 21, 1989." About 50 Duplicates.
  - Framed invitation, Undated; 1 box (Box C.6)
    to a smoker at Princeton Inn, given by Pyne and Benson. (P-11, Yale-6)
  - Golf ball, 1955 June 10; 1 box (Box 11)
    Golf ball marked "I Beat Bill Campell."
    Given by Stanley W. Root, Jr. '45
  - Jewelry, 1922; 1 box (Box C.1)
    Gold Football watch fob. "R.W. Wingate Quarterback. 1922 Champions. P-3, Y-0. P-10, H3."
    Class of 1925
    letter enclosed. Given by Mrs. R.W. Wingate.
  - Megaphone, Undated; 1 box (Box C-Open (under stairs))
    Black with orange "P". Cheerleading.
  - Plate, 1973; 1 box (Box C.1)
    "Princeton-Yale Football Centennial" around edge, "1873-1973" and November 17, 1973 in center, with tiger, bulldog and football. Pewter.
  - Postcard, 1908; 1 box (Box C.1)
    June 6, 1908 Princeton-3 Yale-2. With tiger.
  - Tile, 1939; 1 box (Box C.1)
    1939. Princeton-20, Yale-7. "In the class' service"
  - Wooden Block, Undated; 1 box (Box C.1)
    with tiger and football helmet.
    Made for Austin P Leland, inherited by Donald Griffin
- Series 13: Stamps, 1956; 6 boxes
  The Stamps Series includes stamps, pins, a plaque and an umbrella.
  - 200th Anniversary stamp, 1956; 1 box (Box 11)
    200th Anniversary of Nassau Hall stamp. Glass container engraved on front "John T. Root '53."
  - Framed stamps and envelope, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    White stamps with green picture of football player and coach. Red lettering "Football, 1869-1969."
    Separated from AC180. No prior provenance known.
  - Postage stamp, 1956; 1 box (Box Z.7)
    $.03; 200th anniversary of Nassau Hall.
  - Stamp, 1956; 1 box (Box E.1)
    200th Anniversary of Nassau Hall 1756-1956. $.03 US postage. In paperweight of Don Griff '23.
  - Stamp, 1956; 1 box (Box E.1)
    AR.2000.117
    First day cover for Nassau Hall 200th Anniversary.
  - Wooden Block stamp, Undated; 1 box (Box E.1)
    University insignia, books, diploma with Latin. 2".
  - Wooden Block stamp, Undated; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Tiger with "P" on chest.
- Series 14: Tobacco, 1870-1973; 18 boxes
  The Tobacco series contains Princeton-themed tobacco accessories and packaging.
  - Ashtray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Round with university seal. Green ceramic.
  - Ashtray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.34)
    AR.1996.043
    White ceramic with tiger, "54."
    Class of 1954
  - Ashtray, 1954; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Glass, "Princeton Triangle Show 1/2/54 'Malice in Wonderland' 60th anniversary."
  - Ashtray, 1973; 1 box (Box A.40)
    Reunions. Class of 1923 50th. White with gold edge, with shield and tiger.
  - Ashtray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.40)
    "Princeton" and shield. Pewter and china.
  - Ash Tray, 1949; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Class of 1904 45th Reunion 1949. Round, orange.
  - Ash Tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    Classical Seminary Princeton University. Metal.
  - Ash Tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.34)
    University seal. Rectangular, white and green-brown.
  - Ash Tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    EX5007